so let's see if we understand the
differences between message passing and
shared memory if we have a program in
which one core knows how to initialize
an array and then all others need to
read the entire array then the number of
lines of code for the data distribution
of the array once it has been
initialized does message passing have
fewer lines of code and share memory for
this does it have about equal number of
lines of code or do you think that it
gets more lines of code than shared
memory in which case write a larger than
sign and then once we have achieved data
distribution
synchronization that is needed to make
sure that the initialization is done
before we can read the array adds how
many lines of code in a message passing
version of the code and in the shared
memory version of the code you only need
to say whether it's zero or larger than
zero